Jacky Zhao

Front-End Developer

Contact

Phone:

647-966-9426

E-mail:

zhao.jackyy@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/jackyyyzzz

GitHub:

github.com/jackyyyzzz

Portfolio:

jackyyyzzz.github.io

Software

Front-End:

React, Redux

HTML, CSS/LESS/SASS, VanillaJS

Bootstrap, jQuery

GraphQL, Socket.io, Ember.js

AJAX, JSON, XML, APIs

Back-End:

Node.js, Express.js, Ejs, PHP

Database:

MongoDB, Mongoose

MySQL

Others:

Webpack, Babel, NPM

Adobe Photoshop/XD, MS Office

Summary

I am a self-taught Front-End Developer with about 1 year of experience on building and maintaining responsive websites. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript; plus, modern libraries and frameworks such as React/Redux. Looking for a junior position to excel in the field of software development.

Work Experiences

2019-10 -Current

Freelance Web Developer

Remote, Toronto

- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects.
- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement.
- Maintained strict budgetary and scheduling guidelines to satisfy customers with high-quality, targeted designs.
- Tested websites and performed troubleshooting prior to deployment.
- Analyzed requirements and designed, developed and implemented software applications for multiple websites.
- Collected, defined and translated user requirements into project designs and implementation plans.
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Created eye catching and functional digital design concepts across various platforms to strengthen company brand and identity.
- Maintained and supported Apple Macintosh and Windows PC for end users.
- Converted mockups into HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON.
- Designed sites to be compatible with top browsers, including
 Firefox, Chrome and Safari.

2019-04 -Current

Badminton Coach

Iplay Badminton, Markham, Ontario

- Boosted performance of individual athletes by devising strategic personal training programs.
- Readied athletes for tough games by implementing coordinated regimens of practices and physical conditioning.
- Introduced games and drills, which helped students to better

Skills Time management Excellent Budgeting Excellent Website optimization Very Good Web user interfaces Very Good Testing and debugging

Languages

English

Chinese

Very Good

develop skill levels.

- Developed game plans and adjusted to meet various game situations.
- Motivated athletes to become stronger, more agile and more effective through training habits and proper nutrition.
- Evaluated tapes of competition matches to assess strategies and plan counter approaches.
- Reminded athletes and coaching staff to display and promote good sportsmanship with competing teams on and off field.

Education

2019-05 -	Web Development
2019-09	Udemy - Online
2011-09 - 2019-04	Bachelor of Science: Mathematics
	McMaster University - Hamilton, ON
2016-09 - 2017-04	Aviation
	Confederation College - Thunderbay, ON